(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
MAKE IT, BREAK IT
FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE
Yeah, this is FLOW GLOW from hololive DEV_IS.
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
FLOW GLOW 3Dお披露目ライブ、MAKE IT, BREAK IT だ！
It's the FLOW GLOW 3D Debut Live, MAKE IT, BREAK IT!
楽しむ準備できてますかー！
Are you ready to have fun?!
Yeah, 導体ぶっ放すエンジン 第七感持ってる源氏
Yeah, the engine blasts the conductor, Genji with the seventh sense.
ロックするこの世界全人類 この5人でゲームをチェンジ
Locking onto all of humanity in this world, these five will change the game.
唸る四輪 発射せよ 皆さん サンキュー サランヘヨ
Roaring four wheels, fire away. Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo.
操る二台のターンテーブル 獲る一番ここグランドゼロ
Operating two turntables, taking first place right here at ground zero.
エイ！リスク越えて挑戦 チャンス乗せた打倒線
Ay! Challenge beyond the risk, a overthrowing strike riding on a chance.
昇り詰める頂点 騒乱全歴史笑点
Climbing to the top, the climax of all chaotic history.
乗り込むFG ROADSTER 特殊部隊集合 能力者
Climb into the FG ROADSTER, special forces gathering of psychics.
この歴史に名残 彫刻家 ぶっちぎりでお片付け 孤独車
Leaving a mark on this history, like a sculptor. Blowing past everyone to clean up, in my lone car.
今 光速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now piercing through the atmosphere at the speed of light.
エンジンからジェットの炎入れている火気厳
Jet flames from the engine, strict fire control.
感懐に広がる大帖超えていく海域勢
Crossing the great ledger spreading into the cold sea, sea area power.
バックミラーにPeek-a-boo 映ってるIBM ファイヤー
Peek-a-boo in the rearview mirror, IBM reflected. Fire!
ぶち上げデカい華とんでくウチラ世代
Blasting off, big flowers flying, our generation.
この燃料朽ち果てない イケすぎでしょ シンデレラタイム
This fuel won't rot away. It's too cool, right? Cinderella time.
We are 飛んでデカいビジョン 燃えてるメンバー一途
We are flying with a big vision, the members are burning with single-mindedness.
同 タイム現在進行形 超えてく世界規模
Same time, present progressive, going global.
空腹なモンスター 静かなモンスター エイリアンズサバイバー FGパーティハ
Hungry monster, quiet monster. Aliens survivor, FG party is...
光出すロードスター ヘビーブースター 目覚めてく本能は 青い炎
The shining roadster, heavy booster. The awakening instinct is a blue flame.
We are fans, let's go out 情けない風を食らわす 空まで 飛んで 走るFGモンスター
We are fans, let's go out. Making the pathetic wind eat dust. Flying to the sky, running, the FG monster.
唸るブースター FG ROADSTER 3D 今 Chase me
Roaring booster, FG ROADSTER 3D, now chase me.
プロミのみんな、楽しんでますかー！
Everyone in the Promise, are you having fun?!
FGちゃんたちも、もっともっとかます準備できてるー？
Are you FG girls ready to kick it up even more?
FG ROADSTERに続いてはこの曲、24K GOLD だ！
Following FG ROADSTER is this song, 24K GOLD!
我々、駆け抜けれスーパーカー 金ピカの光 異次元
We are the supercars racing through. A gold brilliance from another dimension.
荒れ果てた世界パトロール 掻き払って踊れ
Patrolling the desolate world, sweep it away and dance.
私たち存在がジャンキー
Our very existence is junkies.
いつでも万端な準備
Always fully prepared.
まるで無敵の宇宙人
Like invincible aliens.
ジュンジュン リアル今準備
Jun-jun, really preparing now.
サイコブレイク ナイツげき
Psycho Break, night's play.
ハイボルテージ 毎度ステキ
High voltage, always wonderful.
最速でIS 愛を送る
At the highest speed, IS, sending love.
今の勝ってる波のウェーブ
The winning wave right now.
1、2、3番地 最新の
Lot 1, 2, 3, the latest.
みんなで遊ぼう 最近どう？
Let's all play together. How've you been lately?
流れてるアブローラー 哀気道
The flowing ab-roller, aikido.
戦闘力 マイデザイン
Combat power, my design.
やるじゃん 100%
Not bad, 100%.
この爆発力は含蓄
This explosive power has depth.
目つきに興味ないルパン三世
Lupin III who's not interested in looks.
この輝きならばいざカミング
If it's this brilliance, then come on.
神風、受けなびかせ ククク病バレ レベルアップ ップップップップ
Kamikaze, catch it and let it flutter. Heh heh heh, the sickness is exposed. Level up-pup-pup-pup-pup-pup.
心を突き動かせ ククク病バレ レベルアップ ップップップップ
Stir your heart. Heh heh heh, the sickness is exposed. Level up-pup-pup-pup-pup-pup.
Look at me なびまとうプライス スーツは 24K GOLD Ready to go
Look at me, draped in price. The suit is 24K GOLD, Ready to go.
深い闇照らす輝き 24K GOLD Ready you go
A brilliance that lights up the deep darkness. 24K GOLD, Ready you go.
空飛んでるワッサー
Flying in the sky, wassup.
このケープがスーパーっす
This cape is super cool.
見なぎってるパワーは
The power that's overflowing...
戦ってるスーパーガール
...is a fighting super girl.
全身駆け巡る満タンのガソリン
A full tank of gasoline running through the whole body.
黄金の流星だ パッと見
At first glance, a golden meteor.
忍者みたいハンズアップ 激アツ
Like a ninja, hands up, super hot.
弱点からいってかっこいい
Starting from my weaknesses, so cool.
戦う 高まる
Fighting, rising.
黄金の精神 現る
The golden spirit appears.
渋谷 新宿 原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku.
風となりちはやぶる
Becoming the wind, mighty and fierce.
絶体絶命 命令ない
Desperate situation, no orders.
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
An elite squad like the Avengers.
生成AIにはないオーラ
An aura that generative AI doesn't have.
盛ってる輝く生命体
A shining living being that stands out.
受けなびかせ ぐぐぐっ ぴょぱれ
Catch the breeze, gu-gu-gu pyopare
Ready lock, go go go go go go go!
心を 吹き動かせ
Let your heart be moved
ぐぐぐっ ぴょぱれ Let it pop pop pop pop pop!
gu-gu-gu pyopare, Let it pop pop pop pop pop!
向かい風に身をまとい進むは
Clad in a headwind, moving forward
24K GOLD READY TO GO READY TO GO GO!
深い闇照らす輝き
The radiance that shines through deep darkness
解き放て 黄金の戦士 FLOW GLOW!
Unleash it, the golden warriors, FLOW GLOW!
FG!
Vroom!
FG! FG! FG! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
FG!
Flow Glow!
Flow Glow 3Dライブお披露目の
Everyone watching Flow Glow's
ご覧の皆さん、What's up!
3D live debut, what's up!
We are Flow Glow!
先ほどはFGロードスターと
Just now, we performed a medley
24K GOLDをメドレー形式でお届けしました！
of FG Roadster and 24K GOLD!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いや、最初からド派手な登場すぎませんか？
Man, wasn't that a super flashy entrance?
まあね、どうやったらみんなを
Well, we thought about how we could
あっと驚かせられるか考えた結果だよね！
really surprise everyone!
そうなんだよね、一番ド派手なもんで行こうって言って
Exactly, we said let's go with the flashiest way,
モニターを突き破ってきました！
so we burst right through the monitor!
やりすぎ！聞いたことないわ！
Too much! I've never heard of that!
そんな破天荒すぎる私たちなんですけど、まずはね
That's how wild we are, but first,
自己紹介の方からさせていただけたらなと思います！
I'd like to start with the introductions!
それでは私から！
Starting with me!
私の音に合図！Riana in the house!
Signal to my beat! Riana in the house!
Flow Glowのリーダー、五十嵐梨杏です！ブラブラ〜！
The leader of Flow Glow, Isaki Riana here! Bra-bra!
次はニコ！
Next is Niko!
ニコたんが来たー！
Niko-tan has arrived!
ホロライブデバイス、Flow Glowのお笑い担当
Hololive DEV_IS, Flow Glow's comedy specialist,
虎金ニコです！ニコたんだよ〜！
Kogane Niko! It's Niko-tan!
すーちゃん！
Su-chan!
しゅぴしゅわ〜！すーの充電、足りてる？
Shupishuwa! Is Su's battery charged?
ホロライブデバイス、Flow Glowのエライ宣伝担当
Hololive DEV_IS, Flow Glow's Great Promotion Specialist,
水宮すうです！
Mizumiya Su here!
次はちは！
Next is Chiha!
ハイ！エンジン全開 Let's Go!
Hi! Engine full throttle, Let's Go!
Flow GlowのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千速です！
Flow Glow's DJ and driver, Rindo Chiharu here!
今日も盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's have a blast today!
次はビビ！
Next is Vivi!
はーい！いきますよ、せーの！ビビ！
Hi! Here we go, one, two... Vivi!
いつもキラキラな、綺々羅々ヴィヴィです！
Always sparkling, Kikirara Vivi here!
みんな今日も盛り上がっていきましょう！よろしく！
Everyone, let's get hyped today! Nice to meet you!
今日は私たち5人で最高のライブをお届けしていくぞ！
Today, the five of us will deliver the best live show ever!
さて、すでにお気づきかとは思いますが、ついに
Now, you've probably noticed by now, but finally...
Flow Glowも3Dデビューしました！
Flow Glow has made its 3D debut!
そりゃ気づくよね！こんだけ動いてたらね！
Of course they noticed! We're moving around so much!
ちなみにビビ、3Dになった自分の体を見てどう思いますか？
By the way Vivi, how do you feel seeing your 3D body?
いや、こんなにキューティー・セクシー・ヘルシーでね
Man, it's so cutie, sexy, and healthy...
みんなもっとビビのこと好きになっちゃったな、ほんまや〜！
everyone's gonna fall for Vivi even more, for real!
ハイ、ありがとね！千速はどう？
Okay, thank you! Chiharu, how about you?
はい！千速はもちろん、この太もも！見てください！
Yes! For me, of course, it's these thighs! Look at them!
もっと見て！もっと見て！
Look more! Look more!
絶対領域決まってるからね！ハイタイプだからね！
My absolute territory is perfect! Since I'm the tall type!
すーちゃんはどうですか？
What about you, Su-chan?
はい、すーはまぁ、カッコいいかな？みたいな
Yeah, I think I look... cool? Or something.
イケてるかな？みたいなね！
Like, I look pretty fly!
いや、水宮ってカッコいい！
Wow, Mizumiya is so cool!
いや、そんなキャラじゃなかったよ！お嬢ちゃんね！
Wait, that wasn't your character! You're a young lady!
バレちゃったな！カッコいい！
You caught me! I'm cool!
ニコたん！
Niko-tan!
ニコたん完全に虎！ほら！
Niko-tan is completely a tiger! Look!
さっきまで二足歩行じゃなかった？
Weren't you walking on two legs just now?
いや、ライブで踊るんだから四足にはできないでしょ！
Well, I'm dancing in a live show, so I can't be on all fours!
梨杏はどうですか？
How about you, Riana?
そうですね、まあ、私も、やっぱりセクシー！
Let's see, well, I'm also... sexy as expected!
セクシーや！すごい似合ってるよね！
You're sexy! It really suits you!
このセクシーダンスをね、お披露目できるかなと思うとすごく嬉しいです！
I'm so happy to be able to show off this sexy dance!
素晴らしい！可愛くて楽しみですね！
Wonderful! You're cute and I'm looking forward to it!
そんな5人でお届けするライブの、ハッシュタグについてニコよろしく！
Niko, please explain the hashtag for today's live with the five of us!
はーい！今日の3Dライブのハッシュタグ、右上をご覧ください！
Okay! Check the top right for today's 3D live hashtag!
ハッシュタグ #FG3Dライブ です！
It's hashtag #FG3DLive!
切り抜きやスクショに加えて、Xでたくさんポストしてください！
Please post lots on X with clips and screenshots!
お願いします！トレンド1位目指すぞ！
Please! Let's aim for #1 on trending!
あとライブを見てくれてるみんな！コメントで声援を送ってください！
Also, everyone watching! Please send us your cheers in the comments!
よろしくお願いします！待ってます！
Thank you! We're waiting for them!
はいそしたらライブの後半には、えーサプライズや重大発表もありますので、
Alright, there will be surprises and major announcements in the latter half of the live,
是非最後まで楽しんでいただけると嬉しいです。
so I hope you enjoy until the very end.
お願いします！
Please do!
最後まで、まばたきしないでね！
Don't blink until the end!
てかさ千早さ、フウタロウ置いてるのまずいかも。
Anyway Saki, leaving Futaro here might be bad.
だめなの？かっこいいよ。
Is it not allowed? It's cool though.
いや、東京あのアの路上駐車だめ。
No, street parking in Tokyo is a no-go.
切っちゃうよ、切っちゃうよ。ほら路上駐車切っちゃう。やめなさい。ほらダメ。やめなさい。
They'll ticket it. See, street parking gets ticketed. Stop it. No. Stop.
だからあの、ま、あの繋いでおくから止めてきてもらって。
So, um, well, I'll keep the talk going so you can go park it.
あ、止めてきてくれる？
Oh, will you go park it?
もちろん。待ってるから。
Of course. We'll wait.
まかせてね。行ってきます。
Leave it to me. I'm off.
じゃあ次の曲いこうか。
Then let's go to the next song.
続いての曲だね。
The next song.
ま、冗談はさておき、えー1曲目から『FG Roadstar』と『24K GOLD』をメドレー形式でお送りしてきました。
Well, jokes aside, we've presented a medley starting from 'FG Roadstar' and '24K GOLD'.
なんと、その『FG Roadstar』のサビの振り付けは、すーちゃんがしてくれたんだよね！
And, Isui-chan choreographed the chorus of 'FG Roadstar'!
ふー、ふー、ふー！やっぱりね、ちょっとかっこいい感じで。
Whoo, whoo, whoo! As expected, it has a cool feel.
あ！パッパッ。あちはありがとう！公道車検は守れよ！
Ah! Pa-pa. Thanks Saki! Keep the public road inspection up!
そう、かっこいい感じでね、ここからの振りを、作らせていただいたんですけど。
Yeah, with a cool vibe, I got to create the choreography from here.
あ、いいよね、かっこいいよね。皆さんもね、是非いつか踊ってください。よろしくお願いします。
Ah, it's good, it's cool. Everyone, please dance to it someday. Thank you.
ビビ太はメドレーやってみてどうだった？
Bibita, how was doing the medley?
いや、やっぱりずっとね、皆さんに見てもらうのを楽しみにしていて。
Well, I've always been looking forward to everyone seeing it.
リリースした時から、歌とダンス一緒に見てほしいなと思ってたから、
Ever since it was released, I've wanted you to see the singing and dancing together.
こうしてついに皆さんに、見てもらうことができて、めっちゃ嬉しいです！かっこよかったやろ？
So I'm really happy that you could finally see it like this! It was cool, wasn't it?
かっこよかったよー！めっちゃかっこよかったよね。
It was cool! It was really cool, right?
ニコはどうやった？ニコも楽しかった。やっぱなんかこういろんな曲をさ、
How about you, Niko? Niko had fun too. Like, putting various songs together...
こうくっつけてね、踊るとか。ちょっと今ごめん、頭真っ白で何喋ってるのか全くわかんないや。リナはどうやった？
...and dancing. Sorry, my mind's gone blank and I have no idea what I'm talking about. How about you, Rina?
そうだね。でもやっぱデビュー当初からさ、出して、ちょっと待ってちょっと。緊張してる？大丈夫？
Right. But since our debut... wait, hold on. Are you nervous? You okay?
みんな緊張しちゃってる。深呼吸、深呼吸、深呼吸しよ。
Everyone's getting nervous. Deep breath, deep breath, let's take a deep breath.
ふー、ふー、はー。どしたどしたどした。緊張しすぎ。前髪直してあげて。
Phew... What's wrong? You're too nervous. Fix her bangs.
4人の感想をね、あの、言いたかったんだけど。うちも緊張してボロボロ。何も言えない。
I wanted to say what the four of us thought, but I'm nervous and falling apart too. I can't say anything.
やっぱりね、デビューしてから2曲出したね、オリジナル曲を
Being able to perform the two original songs we've released since our debut
こうして皆さんの前で動きありでね、披露することができて本当にね、素敵でしたし、
with movement in front of everyone was truly wonderful.
もうこれからもね、FLOW GLOWのことをずっとよろしくお願いします。
Please keep supporting FLOW GLOW from now on too.
早い早い！泣かないで。これからだから。こっからよ。これからだぞ。FLOW GLOWは。
Too soon! Don't cry. We're just getting started. It's from here. This is it. FLOW GLOW is...
ありがと。デコ感謝ありがと。あ、止めてきてくれたのもありがと。
Thanks. Thanks for the gratitude. Oh, and thanks for going to park it.
そうだね、ちょっとね、ファンの人の車が多すぎて全然空いてなくて。パレード状態。
Yeah, well, there were too many fans' cars and no spots left. It was like a parade.
止めてきちゃったから、今。言うとくけど。帰り気つけよう。危ないからね。
I just finished parking it. Just so you know. Let's be careful on the way back. It's dangerous.
じゃあそろそろ、みんなもライブ見たいかなって思うので、次の曲に参りたいと思います。ついでにモニターも、なんか新しいものになりました。
Well, it's about time, I think everyone wants to see the live, so we'll move on to the next song. Also, the monitor has become something new.
ごめんなさい、すいません。本当にごめんなさい。ありがとうございます。
I'm sorry, excuse me. Really sorry. Thank you.
じゃあね、まだまだライブは続くので、ますます盛り上がっていきましょう！
Well then, the live still continues, so let's get even more excited!
それでは聴いてください、『LOAD』。
Now, please listen to 'LOAD'.
読み込みが完了しました。
Loading complete.
1, 2, 3, Jump!
Show up! 世界中に配信する Life ここは本能
Show up! Streaming Life to the whole world, this is instinct.
80億の星のライティング照らす心
8 billion stars' lighting illuminates the heart.
土が鳴る Time to show my digital bubble
The ground rumbles, time to show my digital bubble.
眠らせない朝まで 鳴る音文字の上
Won't let you sleep until morning, on top of the echoing letters.
どこにいても今日も歌詞を書いてるノートに
No matter where I am, today too, in the notebook where I'm writing lyrics.
変わる景色そっと気付けば板屋東京
The scenery changes softly, and before I know it, I'm in Itaya, Tokyo.
パノラマ見下ろす街 目的地に向かうボート
A town looking down on a panorama. A boat heading to its destination.
瞳に見せろよそっと 力になれる言葉を
Show it to your eyes softly, words that can become strength.
願わくばこのステージ 見てるだけじゃ意味ない
If I may wish, this stage, it's no use just watching.
目じゃなくなった夢 負けず嫌いで有名
The dream is no longer just in my eyes, famous for being a sore loser.
どこにもない修正 君と見た星空の下へ
A correction that's nowhere else. To under the starry sky I saw with you.
届きそうな手
A hand that seems like it could reach.
このデバイスがあればどこへでも行ける気がするよ
If I have this device, I feel like I can go anywhere.
ツーウェイ Say with me by my side
Two-way, say with me by my side.
行こうぜ 二人で
Let's go together.
この地球からバーチャルワールド 気にしない今何時
From this Earth to the virtual world. Doesn't matter what time it is.
何キロ離れてても My ジブラルタル
No matter how many kilometers apart, my Gibraltar.
届くこの動悸開始 他愛もない前途
This heartbeat starts to reach. Insignificant future.
調子がいい今日カメラにする配置
Doing well today, the arrangement I'll put on camera.
見てみなこの最大 負ける気しない 全ては僕らの愛
Look at this maximum. Don't feel like losing. Everything is our love.
できるよここじゃない 狙うは宵っ張りの愛
We can do it, not here. Aiming for the love of the night owls.
響け愛のある最大
Resonate, the greatest love.
やるなら指の先まで
If you're gonna do it, do it to the tips of your fingers.
Show up! 世界中に配信する Life ここは本能
Show up! Streaming Life to the whole world, this is instinct.
80億の星のライティング照らす心
8 billion stars' lighting illuminates the heart.
土が鳴る Time to show my digital bubble
The ground rumbles, time to show my digital bubble.
眠らせない朝まで 鳴る音文字の上
Won't let you sleep until morning, on top of the echoing letters.
どこにいても今日も歌詞を書いてるノートに...
No matter where I am, today too, in the notebook where I'm writing lyrics...
変わる景色外
The scenery outside changes
気づけばいたよ東京
Before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空見る下を
Looking at the night sky below
まる月に向かうバト
A battle heading towards the full moon
みんなに見せるよ証拠
I'll show everyone the proof
力になれる言葉を
With words that can give strength
一世一代しか遊べない
You can only play once in a lifetime
どう生きるか全部武器にしたい
I want to turn how I live into a weapon
好きなように生きていける世界で
In a world where you can live as you like
広げていけるこの視界
Expanding this field of vision
100人いる今日も
There are 100 people today too
歌詞を書いてるノートに
In the notebook where I write lyrics
変わる景色外
The scenery outside changes
気づけばいたよ東京
Before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空見る下を
Looking at the night sky below
まる月に向かうバト
A battle heading towards the full moon
みんなに見せるよ証拠
I'll show everyone the proof
力になれる言葉を
With words that can give strength
パジャマのままチョイスするMorning meal
Choosing morning meal while still in pajamas
頭空っぽになるルーティン
The routine that empties my head
始まりから終わりまでMusic
Music from beginning to end
Screen Screen Screen
朝起きてえらい
Good job for waking up in the morning
傘持ってえらい
Good job for bringing an umbrella
ネガティブありえない
No way to be negative
自由に気分をリライト
Rewrite my mood freely
背伸びしない 遠慮しない ヤバいくらい
Don't overreach, don't hold back, dangerously
ゆるい間合い
Loose interval
描いてカラーバーストしたい
I want to draw and have a color burst
落ちない話 続ける
Keep talking about stories that don't fall
喜怒哀楽 決めないってフリースタイル
Freestyle by not deciding emotions
指差されたけど気分はフライ
Got pointed at but feel like flying
眠たい眠たい
Sleepy, sleepy
眠らないTonight
Won't sleep tonight
無敵な状態
Invincible state
代われ代われは調子に乗って言ってお母さんが言ってた
Saying 'take turns, take turns' while being carried away, Mom said
フィルター越しのスナップでPeace
Peace with a snap through a filter
本当のことは虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクもJust Like a piece
Real and fake are just like a piece
So decide what we are
Knock back Good enough
I'm sick Good enough
Chill out Good enough
More view Good enough
I'm sick Good enough
Knock back Good enough
5時 7時 三朝三時 また寝過ごし 寝過ごし
5 o'clock, 7 o'clock, 3:30 AM, overslept again, overslept
でも生きてる証
But it's proof I'm alive
未完成だからこそ作れる Good enough
I can make it precisely because it's incomplete, Good enough
磨けば必ず光るはず Good enough
It should definitely shine if polished, Good enough
夢見てた頃の自分は最強 街集めたフル装備バイビビビ
The me who was dreaming was the strongest, full equipment collected in town, Bi-Bi-Bi
だからこそ高鳴るマイほめたいほめたい 邪魔に褒められたい
That's why my heart beats, want to praise, want to praise, want to be praised by the nuisance
言葉じゃ足りない
Words are not enough
愛想がいいの赤ちゃんの時からっておばあちゃんも言ってた
Grandma said I've been friendly since I was a baby
パジャマのままチョイスするMorning meal
Choosing morning meal while still in pajamas
頭空っぽになるルーティン
The routine that empties my head
始まりから終わりまでMusic
Music from beginning to end
Screen So feel it trouble anywhere
Knock back Good enough
I'm sick Good enough
Chill out Good enough
More view Good enough
I'm sick Good enough
フィルター越しのスナップでPeace
Peace with a snap through a filter
本当のことは虹の彼方に
The truth is beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクもJust Like a piece
Real and fake are just like a piece
So decide what we are
パジャマのままチョイスするMorning meal
Choosing morning meal while still in pajamas
頭空っぽになるルーティン
The routine that empties my head
始まりから終わりまでMusic Screen
Music Screen from beginning to end
NEXT
PERFORM THE PERFORMANCE
Isaki Riona
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
SOLO PERFORMANCE
Oh... yeah... / La la la...
ダリア / 作詞: ちゃんみな / 作曲: ちゃんみな / Ryosuke "Dr.R" Sakai
Dahlia / Lyrics: Chanmina / Composition: Chanmina / Ryosuke "Dr.R" Sakai
Once upon a time
There was a little girl
君によく似た
Who looked a lot like you
Oh darling
君に似ていた
She resembled you
彼女はまるでタイガーアイ
She was just like a Tiger's Eye
無数の欲より大事な夢を見つけては
Finding a dream more important than countless desires
掴んでしまった
And grabbing hold of it
ある夜 雨が降ってた
One night, it was raining
濡れた目に ぼやけた
Blurry through teary eyes
嘘のように美しい
Unbelievably beautiful
ダリアが微笑んでた
Dahlia was smiling
I was the same one
それが押し退け 掻き捨て 越いた
Pushing aside, throwing away, surpassing it
引き換えに何かが欲しい
Wanting something in return
奏でる賛美歌
A hymn being played
無知なメロディはハイ
The ignorant melody is high
誰かが心の蕾を
Someone [took] the bud of the heart
差し上げた夢を...
The dream I offered up...
余った願い
The remaining wishes
そして彼女は
And then she...
ダンサーダリアのように
Like a dancer, like Dahlia
ダリア
Dahlia
改めまして、伊崎莉緒奈です！
Once again, I'm Riona Isaki!
名前、覚えて帰ってください！
Please remember my name before you leave!
Upboomboom / 作詞: MOMONADY / cono / 作曲: Giga & TeddyLoid
Upboomboom / Lyrics: MOMONADY / cono / Composition: Giga & TeddyLoid
斬新 難心 邁進 エコー / Up, down, always getting to trouble
Innovative, difficult heart, pushing forward, echo / Up, down, always getting to trouble
楽しい 正しい 嬉しい でも
Fun, right, happy, but
平常心 さあ あれなーし
Calmness, well, none of that
これなし 合わせる段々的 なし
Not this, no gradual adjustment
己の辺 高鳴る ノノノノノ
My surroundings throb, no no no no no
またゼロベース Get away! Oh no no no no
Back to zero base, Get away! Oh no no no no
Whisper goodbye, oh give me some more, that's
手招きして 価値なウェイ / Steppin' up break it down
Beckoning, a worthy way / Steppin' up break it down
噛ませ 苦情ショー
Give 'em a grievance show
放て 自己中ウェイ ナウ
Release the selfish way now
Oh, べべっしょう だから ガラガラショウ / I'm shaking it goes next
Oh, baby show, so it's a clattering show / I'm shaking it goes next
Hungry so what? Though
Come again look here / Show me what you got break it up beat it me
サイネキ
Sineki
サイネキ アネキ ネキネキサイネキ
Sineki aneki nekineki saineki
魂んだれ Upboomboom
Pour your soul, Upboomboom
Trippin' the dark, yeah / That's funny safe for me
To explain, shake it up easy you don't understand
I just wanna make it loud
ルールはない ぜ
There are no rules
頭と心 Wake now
Head and heart, Wake now
アブラカタブラブラブラ 幻なら無理無理
Abracadabra-bra-bra, if it's a phantom, impossible
勝ちなし 無視 ああ Just do it / Are you ready? Let's play game
No victory, ignore, ah Just do it / Are you ready? Let's play game
万事 万事 愛しては / 一蓮托生 3000 世界
Everything, everything, loving them / Bound together in fate, three thousand worlds
乱心 等身 倒心 Get out / 全方位ご覧
Distracted heart, life-size, falling heart, Get out / Look in all directions
Dice be my life / Be my life / I will stage to work it up all ready move
曇りなく居たいだろう
You want to be without cloudiness, right?
Anything you need though / Oh I wanna be more
たまには我がままになって / 画面立ち上がりラウ
Becoming selfish once in a while / Standing up from the screen loud
鳴らせ 鼓動を
Sound your heartbeat
覚ませ 最高潮 ウェイ ナウ
Awaken the climax, way now
Oh, べべっしょう だから ガラガラショウ
Oh, baby show, so it's a clattering show
Oh, べべっしょう だから ガラガラショウ / I'm shaking it goes next
Oh, baby show, so it's a clattering show / I'm shaking it goes next
Hungry so what? Though
Come again look here / Show me what you got break it up beat it me
サイネキ
Sineki
サイネキ アネキ ネキネキサイネキ
Sineki aneki nekineki saineki
魂んだれ Upboomboom
Pour your soul, Upboomboom
Na na na... Daria... / Let's make it loud...
Saineki saineki... / Pour your soul Upboomboom
魂んだれ Upboomboom
Pour your soul, Upboomboom
欲望に満ちた青年団
A youthful group full of desire
作詞・作曲：Taka
Lyrics/Composition: Taka
一度はあの光を見たんだよ
I once saw that light
とっても綺麗で
It was so beautiful
でも今思えば汚かった
But looking back now, it was dirty
あれはいわゆるBad Day
It was what they call a bad day
光が眩しすぎて周りが見えず　ただただ道を
The light was too bright to see around me, just following the path
歩んでたあの日の自分を
I can laugh at myself from those days
今なら笑えるよ
When I was just walking along
一度はあの幕を開けたんだよ
I once opened that curtain
とっても重くて
It was so heavy
プレッシャー、闇、それに勝つために
Pressure, darkness, to overcome those
ただ嫌な奴で
I was just a nasty person
そして気が付くと真っ暗な部屋に　独りぼっちだった
And before I knew it, I was all alone in a pitch-black room
もう二度と戻れないなんて
Saying I can never go back
歩くのもやめた
I even stopped walking
But I know alone, I know alone
We're not, we're not, we're not alone
お金じゃ買えないもの手に入れて
Gaining something that money can't buy
もう一度光浴びて
Basking in the light once more
そして今度は騙されぬように
And this time, so I'm not deceived
僕らは今目指すよ
We're aiming for it now
欲望に満ちた青年団
A youthful group full of desire
誰かが言った言葉
The words someone said
それすらその時は流して
Even those I let slide at the time
今になって気づいたよ
Now I've realized it
欲望に負けた青年団
A youthful group that lost to desire
So I know you know, you know I know
We have, we have, we have it all
ほら笑えないように
So as not to be laughed at
上向いて
Looking up
歩こう
Let's walk
もう一度光浴びて
Basking in the light once more
そして今度は騙されぬように
And this time, so I'm not deceived
僕らは今目指すよ
We're aiming for it now
欲望に満ちた青年団
A youthful group full of desire
誰かが言った言葉
The words someone said
それすらその時は流して
Even those I let slide at the time
今になって気づいたよ
Now I've realized it
欲望に負けた青年団
A youthful group that lost to desire
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much
かがみ
Mirror
作詞・作曲：ヤマモトショウ
Lyrics/Composition: Sho Yamamoto
おはよ
Good morning
朝起きて　まず確認
Wake up and first check
今日もいい感じだな
Looking good today too
1年365日
365 days a year
私のこと一番見てる人
The person who looks at me the most
好きです、と言えるのは
Being able to say "I love you"
当たり前とかじゃない
Is not something to take for granted
1日8万6千400秒
86,400 seconds a day
ずっと付き合ってくんだから
Because we're going to be together forever
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard this from my mom
似た人好きになるんじゃなくて
It's not that you fall for someone like you
好きな人には似るものらしいです
But that you end up becoming like the person you love
本当？
Is it true?
鏡で、みんな思ったことあるわ
In the mirror, everyone has thought about it
目を開けたら違う自分になって
If I open my eyes and I've become someone else
いやいやもっと真剣に
No, no, more seriously
変身！
Transform!
マスカラ塗り直して振る振るるん
Reapplying mascara, shake shake shake
あー 可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Ah, maybe I've become too cute
さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
I might've overdone it with the makeup
あなたのナンバーワンです だって
I'm your number one, because...
超大好きなんだから
...I love you so super much
鏡よ鏡 もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more
可愛くなってもいいのかな
Is it okay if I become even cuter?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest
それで
And then...
秘密 秘密 秘密の可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
I can't be a 'secret, secret, secret cute girl'
そんなこと全部お見通しです
I can see through everything like that
だって 逆に
Because, conversely
秘密 秘密 秘密は私たちにはいらない
Secrets, secrets, we don't need secrets
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど
But so much that you'd want to keep it a secret
可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Maybe I've become too cute
朝起きてそうだ休み
Waking up in the morning, oh right, it's a holiday
やりたいことありすぎ
Too many things I want to do
一日は24時間って言うけど
They say a day has 24 hours, but...
ずっと起きてるわけでもない
...it's not like I'm awake the whole time
帰ったらまた鏡
When I get home, it's the mirror again
当たり前とかじゃない
It's not like it's a given
とにかく自分を大事にしましょう
Anyway, let's take care of ourselves
ずっと付き合ってくんだから
Because we're going to be together forever
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard it from my mom
10時から2時は寝るのがよくて
It's best to sleep from 10 PM to 2 AM
6時以降は食べないほうがいい
And better not to eat after 6 PM
いや無理です
Yeah, that's impossible
みんな思ったことあるわ
Everyone's thought about it
寝てる間に変わらないのかな
I wonder if I won't change while I sleep
いやいややっぱ真剣に変身したい
No, no, I really want to transform for real
マスカラ塗り直して振る振るるん
Reapplying mascara, shake shake shake
あー 可愛くなりすぎていい？
Ah, is it okay to become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎていい？
Is it really okay to overdo it?
あなたのこと好きです だって
I like you, because...
超前向きなんだから
...I'm super positive
鏡よ鏡 もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more
可愛くなってもいいのかな
Is it okay if I become even cuter?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest
もう 大好きで 大好きで
I already love you so much, so much
君に前向きに言っていいのかな
Is it okay to tell your positive self?
自分で今魔法かけます
I'll cast a spell on myself now
嘘でもかかったふりしてね
Pretend it worked, even if it's a lie
でも私もあなたも嘘がつけない
But neither you nor I can lie
そういう奴だからさ
Because we're just that kind of person
マスカラ塗り直して振る振るるん
Reapplying mascara, shake shake shake
あー 可愛くなりすぎていい？
Ah, is it okay to become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎていい？
Is it really okay to overdo it?
あなたのこと好きです だって
I like you, because...
超前向きなんだから
...I'm super positive
鏡よ鏡 もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more
可愛くなってもいいのかな
Is it okay if I become even cuter?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest
あー 可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Ah, maybe I've become too cute
さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
I might've overdone it with the makeup
あなたのナンバーワンです だって
I'm your number one, because...
超大好きなんだから
...I love you so super much
鏡よ鏡 もうちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit more
可愛くなってもいいのかな
Is it okay if I become even cuter?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay honest
それで
And then...
秘密 秘密 秘密の可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
I can't be a 'secret, secret, secret cute girl'
そんなこと全部お見通しです
I can see through everything like that
だって 逆に
Because, conversely
秘密 秘密 秘密は私たちにはいらない
Secrets, secrets, we don't need secrets
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど
But so much that you'd want to keep it a secret
可愛くなりすぎちゃったです
I've become just too cute
青の朔日 / 作詞・作曲: 藤原基央
Blue New Moon / Lyrics & Composition: Motoo Fujiwara
終わらない夜の途中
In the middle of an endless night
明かりを忘れた空には
In the sky that has forgotten its light
戻れない日の指切りを
A pinky swear for days we can't return to
カシオペアの代わりに
Instead of Cassiopeia
独り待った だから
I waited alone, so...
物が落とす影を追っていたら
...while chasing the shadows things cast
真っ暗に紛れて混ざって
Fading and mixing into the pitch black
見つけられないままで
I remain unable to be found
いくつものドアを開けて
Opening numerous doors
繰り返す景色を泳ぐ
I swim through repeating scenery
心がまだ疲れながら
Even while my heart is still weary
そのためだけに動いてる
I'm moving just for that purpose
これはきっと帰り道
This is surely the way home
夢の向こうに続く道
A path continuing beyond dreams
誇れる歌を纏えば
If I clothe myself in a song I can be proud of
何も怖くはない
I'll have nothing to fear
命は理由に出会えた
Life has found its reason
燃えて消える意味を知った
I learned the meaning of burning and disappearing
その陽が視界を照らした
That sun illuminated my vision
青く 青く どこまでも
Blue, blue, as far as the eye can see
明日が全てを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything
あなたの言葉だけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing only your words
ならば私は戦える
Then I can fight
たとえこの耳が聞こえないとしても
Even if these ears cannot hear
思い出せなくなった
I can't remember anymore
虹を覚えてる空には
In the sky that remembers the rainbow
再び叩く音が響くよ
The sound of knocking echoes once again
それでも歩いてると
Even so, as I walk
掴もうとしてすり抜けた
I tried to grab it, but it slipped away
言葉忘れない手のひら
The words I won't forget, in my palm
指を蓋にして隠して
Hiding it with my fingers as a lid
強さに変える魔法を
The magic that turns it into strength
あとどれだけ息をしたら
After how many more breaths
これで良かったと思える
Can I think this was for the best
心がずっと砕けながら
While my heart keeps breaking
かけらの全部で動いてる
It's moving with all its pieces
これはきっと帰り道
This must be the way back
あの日と同じじゃなくていい
It doesn't have to be the same as that day
ただもう一度だけ会いたい
I just want to meet you one more time
何も怖くない
I'm not afraid of anything
泣かないで祈るのは
What I'm praying for without crying
足跡の下の涙
Are the tears under my footprints
迷いを乗せた爪先で
With my toes carrying my doubts
進め 進め 魂ごと
Move forward, move forward, with my whole soul
正しいかどうか何てことよりも
More than whether it's right or not
あなたのいる世界が笑ってほしい
I want the world you're in to smile
だから私は生きている
That's why I'm alive
時計の針にも奪えない力
A power that even the hands of a clock cannot take away
鳥になった宝物が
The treasure that became a bird
落とす影まだ探してる
Is still looking for the shadow it casts
ああ もう一度だけ会いたい
Ah, I want to meet you one more time
何も怖くない
I'm not afraid of anything
命は理由に出会えた
Life has found its reason
燃えて消える意味を知った
I learned the meaning of burning and disappearing
その日が視界を照らした
That day illuminated my vision
青く 青く どこまでも
Blue, blue, everywhere
明日がすべてを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything
繋げた鼓動だけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing only the heartbeats we've connected
だから私は生きている
That's why I'm alive
かけらの全部で
With all the pieces
泣かないで祈るのは
What I'm praying for without crying
足跡の下の涙
Are the tears under my footprints
迷いを乗せた爪先で
With my toes carrying my doubts
進め 進め 魂ごと
Move forward, move forward, with my whole soul
間違いかどうか何てことよりも
More than whether it's a mistake or not
あなたのいる世界が続いてほしい
I want the world you're in to continue
ならば私は戦える
Then I can fight
たとえその時そばにいないとしても
Even if I'm not by your side at that time
この地球(ほし)全てが上の空
This whole planet is absent-minded
半端な覚悟で来なよ坊や
Don't come with half-hearted resolve, boy
Be a beast 独り言のVivid yeah
Be a beast, a vivid monologue yeah
はめ外すなよ坊や
Don't get carried away, boy
なんでそんなに自信があるんですか?
Why are you so confident?
己で掴んだ結果が当たり前じゃん
The results I've grabbed for myself are only natural
Be a beast 独り言の皮肉 yeah
Be a beast, a cynical monologue yeah
鼻に付くかな坊や
Does it get on your nerves, boy?
お褒めを 栄養を
Praise me, nourish me
目まわし出すときまるのもう一味をよこせ
When things get dizzy and settled, give me another flavor
Go way I'm a baby お前が言いたいどうしたいか提示
Go way I'm a baby, show me what you want to say or do
おかわりはいかがですか?
Would you like seconds?
夢を越えろ そこから 上を向けよ
Surpass your dreams, and look up from there
リアルに上を 上をへ
Realistically, higher and higher
ヴォー ここまで来いよ
Whoa, come this far
Come on baby, come on baby
夢を越えろ Hey
Surpass your dreams, hey
Woah woah woah ここまで来いよ
Woah woah woah, come over here
腹も冷えつくリスクがたまんない
The risk that chills my core is irresistible
安手な安心を手伝うにはなんない
Cheap security won't do a thing to help
次に来る予定も好きにやんな
Do whatever you want with your next plans
離さないよ baby
I won't let go, baby
もうちょい遊んで頂戴
Play with me a little more
馬鹿にしてるってとんでもない
No way I'm making fun of you
俺バイキング食べ放題
I'm an all-you-can-eat buffet
ただ毒にあたってもドンマイ お味のほどはいかがですか
But don't mind if you get poisoned, how does it taste?
夢を越えろ
Surpass your dreams
そこから上を向けよ
Look up from there
リアルに上を上を
Really, go higher and higher
Hey woah woah ここまで来いよ
Hey woah woah, come over here
Come together, Come together
Come together, Come together yeah
夢を越えろ Hey
Surpass your dreams, hey
Woah woah woah ここまで来いよ
Woah woah woah, come over here
待てない 待たない いくらあっても足りない
Can't wait, won't wait, no matter how much, it's not enough
腹一杯 食べたい てめえを焼くサラライ
Wanna eat my fill, roasting you, Sarracenia
赤子の五分五分の胎胞 掘り出し物は手に入れるのが勝負
The fifty-fifty embryo of a baby, it's a battle to get the bargains
足元もくもくスモーク 超高級なフルコース
Smoke billowing at your feet, a super high-end full course
数字等には通ず ウォッチコック上手
Proficient in numbers and such, a skilled watch-cook
もっと食らおうショートポーズ ノンストップな時でゴート ダ トップ オブ ザ トップ
Let's eat more, short pause, goat in non-stop time, to the top of the top
夢を越えろ
Surpass your dreams
そこから上を向けよ
Look up from there
リアルに上を上を
Really, go higher and higher
Hey woah woah ここまで来いよ
Hey woah woah, come over here
Come together, Come together
Come together, Come together yeah
夢を越えろ Hey
Surpass your dreams, hey
Woah woah woah ここまで来いよ
Woah woah woah, come over here
Come together, Come together
Come together, Come together yeah
夢を越えろ Hey
Surpass your dreams, hey
Woah woah woah ここまで来いよ
Woah woah woah, come over here
あれが世界なんて
So that's what the world is
誰の誰の果て
Whose end is it?
恒の星何もいこって
Even the eternal stars are nothing
これだけ悩んだってしょうがないか
I guess there's no use worrying this much
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to think it was all a dream
でも全然燃えないけど助けてよブラザー
I'm not fired up at all, but save me, brother
あらがうだけ若さに負け
Just struggling, losing to youth
Next next lucky lucky lucky
あれを割り切れたらさ
If only I could just accept it
あれを楽なろにとか
Thinking it would be easier
マジ新世界か
Is it really a new world?
アンタ以外は
Except for you
アンタ以外はいらないないない
I don't need anyone but you
アンタならば Happy chappy yeah
If it's you, then Happy chappy yeah
アンタのその手と 私のこの手
Your hand and my hand
繋いだらもう二度と離さないわ
Once joined, I'll never let go
アンタのその手と 私のこの手
Your hand and my hand
掴んだら過去を蒸し返す
If I grab them, I'll bring up the past
Oh my love
ニコたんが来たー！
Nico-tan is here!
エンジン全開、レッツゴー！ 盛り上がっていくぞ、レッツゴー！
Engine at full throttle, let's go! Let's get pumped up, let's go!
FLOW GLOWの充電足りてる？足りてないよな！ 後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞ！
Are your FLOW GLOW batteries charged? I bet they're not! Let's keep the energy up for the second half!
みんなのこと、もっとメラメラにしちゃうぞ！ 後半戦も、せーの、うー、ビビ！
I'm gonna make you all even more fired up! For the second half, here we go... woo, BiBi!
みんなに会えて、とっても幸せです！ 画面の向こうのみんな、声出せ、オラー！
I'm so happy to meet you all! Everyone watching on screen, let's hear your voices, come on!
新しい姿のFLOW GLOWで、新しい曲、聴いてくれ。 MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
With FLOW GLOW's new look, listen to our new song. MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
Make it Break it, Make it Break it, Make it Break it, lock on
マトメが合えば相棒、君こそが相棒
If our eyes meet, we're partners, you're the one
メロつかせる才能 Make it break it, Make it break it
Talent for making them fall, Make it break it, Make it break it
パッと見しててもデモ、中にはサムデモ
Even if you just glance, some demo inside
そのギャップ大凶、あれは最高、ヘイトはシコト Hey so
That gap is a total disaster, it's the best, hate is a joke, hey so
一蓮托生 tonight、退屈に用はない
Being in the same boat tonight, no time for boredom
一戦隠せばじゃない、たらさないしょうがない
It's not about hiding a battle, can't stop, it can't be helped
内らが連れ出す Party Party Party
We'll take you out, Party Party Party
演者は嬉しいでしょ 噛み入る 噛み入る Na
The performers are happy, right? Getting into it, getting into it, na...
置いてかないぜ tie 付いてきて five MCs
We won't leave you behind, tie; keep up with the five MCs.
本気の Friday Night, MAKE IT, BREAK IT
A serious Friday Night, MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
MAKE A REVOLUTION 私を貫け
MAKE A REVOLUTION, pierce through me.
傾け 夢に koi koi koi
Strike a pose, fall in love with the dream, koi koi koi.
NO PLACE FOR NEVER STOP 真ん中ブチ抜け
NO PLACE FOR NEVER STOP, break through the middle.
行け 今日よりな
Go, more than today.
YOU SEE MAKE IT, BREAK IT, MAKE IT, BREAK IT
MAKE IT, BREAK IT, BANG BANG BANG
MAKE IT, BREAK IT
ほら どっちにするの？
Look, which one will it be?
ゾクゾク湧く FLOW GO 前より高揚
The flow wells up with excitement, go! More uplifted than before.
If you wanna be my men よそ見とかはなしで
If you wanna be my men, no looking away.
BURNY もっと HOLLAR もっと HOLLAR 熱くなっちゃって
BURNY, more HOLLAR, more HOLLAR, getting heated up.
BURNY HOLLAR HOLLAR もっと HOLLAR 本気になっちゃって
BURNY HOLLAR HOLLAR, more HOLLAR, getting serious.
置いてかないぜ tie 付いてきて five MCs
We won't leave you behind, tie; keep up with the five MCs.
本気の Friday Night, MAKE IT, BREAK IT
A serious Friday Night, MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
BRAND NEW GENERATION 感じるまま上がれ
BRAND NEW GENERATION, rise up as you feel.
上がれ 狩れに恋降り降り降り
Rise up, let love fall, fall, fall upon the hunt.
ONE SIZE FOR NEVER LIE さあこれ抜け出して
ONE SIZE FOR NEVER LIE, now break out of this.
焦せ 練りはない
Hurry, there's no time to refine.
YOU SEE MAKE IT, BREAK IT, MAKE IT, BREAK IT
MAKE IT, BREAK IT, BANG BANG BANG
MAKE IT, BREAK IT
頭まで MAKE A NOISE!
From head to toe, MAKE A NOISE!
FG 行くぞ！
FG, let's go!
MAKE A REVOLUTION 私を貫け
MAKE A REVOLUTION, pierce through me.
傾け 夢に koi koi koi
Strike a pose, fall in love with the dream, koi koi koi.
NO PLACE FOR NEVER STOP 真ん中ブチ抜け
NO PLACE FOR NEVER STOP, break through the middle.
行け 今日よりな
Go, more than today.
YOU SEE MAKE IT, BREAK IT, MAKE IT, BREAK IT
MAKE IT, BREAK IT, BANG BANG BANG
MAKE IT, BREAK IT
ほら どっちにするの？
Look, which one will it be?
いよいよ次が最後の曲です。
Finally, the next song is our last one.
聴いてください。 stay by my side.
Please listen: 'stay by my side'.
ずっと忘れない みんなとの first day
I'll never forget the first day with everyone.
積もり込めく あれは fake face
Piling up, that was a fake face.
見せ尽くでハリボテ
A façade shown to the fullest.
期待と不安詰め込んで 歩き出したんだ せーので
Packed with expectation and anxiety, we started walking together.
強がってた青臭な花びら
The green petals that were trying to be tough.
でもみんなに気付かされた そのままでええやん
But everyone made me realize, it's fine just as you are.
語ら当たり前じゃない この日々
These days we share aren't just ordinary.
バカになっても一緒にいたい bye bibi
Even if we act like fools, I want to be together, bye bibi.
気付いたら騒がし毎日
Before I knew it, every day was noisy.
違う歩幅 どこに行く私たち
With different strides, where are we heading?
迷う自分 みんなくれる刺激
A lost self, but everyone gives me inspiration.
慣れ合いじゃない これって素敵
It's not just getting cozy, this is wonderful.
まだリーダーって胸張れなくても
Even if I can't proudly call myself a leader yet...
持ってる何かある 盾なる覚悟
There's something I have—the resolve to be a shield.
自分のため 私 歌って踊る
For myself, I sing and dance.
ステージ プロローグ 刻む日々目
The stage prologue, carving out each day.
stay by my side
夜中になってもまだ寝れない yeah
Even when it's late at night, I still can't sleep, yeah.
あとどのくらい
Just how much longer...
出辿り着く あの夢の世界
...until I reach that world of dreams?
初めて会ったあの日
That day we first met.
また輪になって遊んだり
Gathering in a circle and playing again.
ここまで歩いてきた見ゆ
The view from how far we've walked.
今でも覚えてる
I still remember it now.
stay by my side
街角で二人
The two of us on a street corner.
by my side
考えたら一人
When I think about it, I'm alone.
無駄にはならないから
Because it won't go to waste...
あの涙も
...even those tears.
今ここ by my side
Now, right here, by my side.
寄り添ってる隣
Cuddled up right next to me.
ずっと昔 はぐれた炎
The flame that strayed long ago.
夜を必死に照らしたこと
Lighting up the night with all its might.
集まる星は追ったこと
Chasing the gathering stars.
それは波長 これからも送る音
That's the wavelength; the sound I'll keep sending.
暗闇の中見えない a way
A way invisible in the darkness.
道標はあなたの再
The signpost is your presence again.
光をこの手を離さないで
Don't let go of the light, of this hand.
空の始まりより煌めいて
Sparkling more than the dawn of the sky.
幸先いい一人 同じ夢
A lucky one, the same dream.
追い合いじゃない weも一人じゃない
It's not a chase; we're not alone either.
隅々やばい プロローグの宇宙
Insane in every corner, the universe of the prologue.
可能性は未知数 ストリーム配信に夢中
Possibilities are endless, obsessed with streaming.
いつかみんなで行こうわい
Let's all go together someday.
きけラララ セラピービーハッピー 楽しみたい日々
Listen, la-la-la, therapy, be happy, days I want to enjoy.
どこか名詞に込めた四人を
The four of us embedded in nouns somewhere...
私たちはやれるきっと from Lindo
...we can surely do it, from Lindoh.
シナジーで足りてる？
Is the synergy enough?
うー！ BB！
Woo! BB!
エンちゃん カレ let's go!
En-chan, Kare, let's go!
リアナ in da house! オリビア行くぞ！
Riana in da house! Olivia, let's go!
stay by my side
夜中になってもまだ寝れない
Even when it's late at night, I still can't sleep.
Yeah あとどのくらい
Yeah, just how much longer...
出辿り着く あの夢の世界
...until I reach that world of dreams?
初めて会ったあの日
That day we first met.
また輪になって遊んだり
Gathering in a circle and playing again.
ここまで歩いてきた見ゆ
The view from how far we've walked.
今でも覚えてる
I still remember it now.
上がれビート 夜も寝れぬ
Rise up, beat! I can't even sleep at night.
置き去りにした生活リズム 十二ヶ月
A lifestyle rhythm left behind for twelve months.
共にいった振り返る
Looking back on where we went together.
愚痴に持ったりしたっていいんじゃない
Isn't it fine to even have some complaints?
威嚇自己拒否ともない
Without intimidation or self-rejection.
一人で抱え込むんなよ ほら水臭い
Don't bottle it all up alone; look, don't be a stranger.
最後に自分らしくいれ 心配ない
Be yourself in the end, don't worry.
美味いもん食べいこうぜ 次一回
Let's go eat something good next time.
stay by my side
夜中になってもまだ寝れない
Even when it's late at night, I still can't sleep.
で あとどのくらい
And just how much longer...
出辿り着く あの夢の世界
...until I reach that world of dreams?
初めて会ったあの日
That day we first met.
また輪になって遊んだり
Gathering in a circle and playing again.
ここまで歩いてきた見ゆ 今でも覚えてる
The view from how far we've walked, I still remember it now.
音で繋がる
Connected by sound
stay by my side 待ち兼ねて二人
stay by my side, the two of us waiting
stay by my side 考えて独り
stay by my side, thinking alone
無駄にはならないから あの涙も
Because they won't go to waste, even those tears
今ここ stay by my side 寄り添ってる隣
Now here, stay by my side, snuggling next to you
はい！ということで、後半ノンストップで駆け抜けてきましたが…
Yes! And so, we've dashed through the second half non-stop, but...
ご覧の通り、衣装チェンジしてまーす！
as you can see, we've changed our outfits!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いや本当に一人一人の個性がめちゃくちゃ主張されていて素敵！
Wow, everyone's individuality is really standing out, it's wonderful!
にこたんは、かっこいいし！
Niko-tan is cool!
りっちゃんは、もうかっこ可愛いし！
Ri-chan is already cool and cute!
すーたんはもう、可愛すぎるし！
Su-tan is just too cute!
それに、なんたって…
And above all...
ビビたん。
Bibi-tan.
え？
Huh?
可愛いね。
You're cute.
なんなのその言い方w
What's with that way of saying it? lol
そして、ここで嬉しいお知らせがあります！
And now, we have some happy news!
このFLOW GLOWの3Dお披露目ライブ、なんとXのトレンドで1位やってます！
This FLOW GLOW 3D debut live is actually trending #1 on X!
さて、じゃあ、ここまでを振り返っていきたいと思います！
Well then, I'd like to look back on everything so far!
まずはわたくし輪堂りおなが、「ダリヤ」と…あ、「アップブーンブン」のメドレーを披露させていただきました！
First, I, Riona Randou, performed a medley of 'Dahlia' and... ah, 'Up Boom Boom'!
はい！千春がトロンボーンとギターを自分で弾きまして、ギターの弾き語りで「欲望に満ちた青年団」を歌わせていただきました！
Yes! Chihaya played the trombone and guitar herself, and sang 'Yokubou ni Michita Seinendan' while playing the guitar!
はい！そしてビビはですね、メイクを活かした「鏡」という楽曲を歌わせていただきました！
Yes! And I, Bibi, sang a song called 'Kagami' that made use of my makeup!
はい！にこたんは大好きなBUMP OF CHICKENさんの「青の朔日」を実は…
Yes! Niko-tan sang my favorite BUMP OF CHICKEN song, 'Ao no Tsuitachi', and actually...
ギターパッパです！実パッパです！
it was with my guitar-papa! My real papa!
実パッパと演奏させていただいた…
I performed with my real papa...
はい！すーが「サラセニア」と「ギャル」のメドレーを踊らせていただきました！
Yes! Su danced a medley of 'Sarracenia' and 'Gyaru'!
はい！みんなでソロを楽しんでもらった後は、私たちの新曲、そしてライブのタイトルにもなっております「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」を初披露させていただきました！
Yes! After everyone enjoyed the solos, we gave the first performance of our new song and the title of this live, 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT'!
その後は、私たちのこないだ出させていただいたシングル「stay by my side」を披露させていただきました！
After that, we performed our recently released single, 'stay by my side'!
そして、ここで配信を見てくれているみんなにお知らせがあります！
And now, we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream!
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Hi! Well then, please take a look at this! Here you go!
FLOW GLOW 1ST ALBUM FLOW GLOW 2026.01.21 RELEASE!
ファーストアルバム「FLOW GLOW」についてです！発売日は来年1月21日！
It's about our first album 'FLOW GLOW'! The release date is January 21st next year!
そして！冒頭にも言った重大発表がこちら！
And! Here is the major announcement I mentioned at the beginning!
アルバムのリード曲になっている「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」について続報があります！
We have follow-up news about 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT', which is the lead track of the album!
6th single 「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」 2025.11.24 0:00~(JST) digital release
先ほど披露した6thシングル「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のデジタルリリースが決定しました！
The digital release of the 6th single 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT' that we just performed has been confirmed!
デジタルリリースは明日、11月24日です！みんな絶対チェックしてやー！
The digital release is tomorrow, November 24th! Everyone, be sure to check it out!
そして、この「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のMVの公開なんですが…
And about the release of the MV for 'MAKE IT, BREAK IT'...
まあ普段やったら楽曲のリリースとほぼ同時に公開やねんけど…
Well, usually it would be released almost at the same time as the song release, but...
運営さんが「もっともっと良いものにしたい」ということで、公開を延期することになりました。
the management said they 'want to make it even better', so we've decided to postpone the release.
私たちが登場します！
We're making our entrance!
さあ皆さん、どんな内容に仕上がっているか、今からめちゃ楽しみにしててな！
Alright everyone, look forward to seeing how it turned out!
やー、かっこよく踊ったもんね。
Yeah, we danced so coolly.
ダンスとかもね、やったもんね。
We did some dancing and all.
ダンスもね、やりましたよ。
We did dance, didn't we?
はい、続いては千早、おねがいします。
Okay, next up, Chihaya, please.
はい、それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ！
Yes! Now, please take a look at this! Here you go!
「FLOW GLOW」の3D新衣装を身にまとった2人を収録！
Featuring two members in their new "FLOW GLOW" 3D outfits!
ホロカについてです。
This is about Holoka.
一昨日発売された千早と虎のスタートデッキ。
The Chihaya and Niko starter decks that went on sale the day before yesterday.
実は今日のライブでお披露目した新衣装のセカンドカードが収録されているんです。
Actually, they contain "Second" cards featuring the new outfits we debuted in today's live.
みんなにはね、サプライズのつもりで先行してセカンド衣装入れてもらったんですが、びっくりしましたか？
We had them include the second outfits ahead of time as a surprise. Were you surprised?
ばれちゃったね。
The secret's out.
実はね、出てたんだよね。
Actually, they were already out there.
これら2つのスタートデッキは、取り扱いのあるカードショップにて販売中です。気になった方はぜひ手に取ってみてください。
These two starter decks are now on sale at participating shops. Please pick them up if you're interested.
ホロカに関する情報はまだまだあります。こちらもご覧ください。どうぞ。
There's still more info about Holoka. Take a look at this too. Here you go.
「アヤカシ・バーミリオン」では虎金錦 虎の3D新衣装も！？ 12.19 (金) 発売！
Will Kogane-no-Tama Niko's new 3D outfit also be in "Ayakashi Vermillion"?! On sale 12/19 (Fri)!
来月19日発売の新ブースターパック「アヤカシ・バーミリオン」。
The new booster pack "Ayakashi Vermillion," releasing on the 19th of next month.
その中に今日虎がお披露目した新衣装のセカンドが収録されています。
It will include the "Second" card of the new outfit that Niko debuted today.
うそ、マジ！？
No way, really!?
なんだよそれ。えー、ちょっといいな、スタッフさん。
What's up with that? Man, come on, staff.
ヴィヴィとすーちゃんのも早くおねがいしますよ。
Please do Vivi and Su-chan's soon too.
はい、では続いてはすーちゃん、おねがいします。
Okay, next up is Su-chan, please.
ホロライブ公式ぬいぐるみブランド「hololive friends with u」、通称「ホロフレ」。ついに私たちFLOW GLOWの5人が登場します！
The official plushie brand "hololive friends with u," or "Holofre." At last, all five of us from FLOW GLOW are joining!
今年のエキスポで開発中とお知らせしてから、やっと皆さまにお届けできるようになりました！
We announced they were in development at this year's Expo, and now we can finally bring them to you!
注目は髪型や衣装。とにかく再現度がすごい！
Check out the hair and outfits. The level of detail is amazing!
今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、お見逃しなく！
Reservations start tonight at 22:00, so don't miss out!
続いてのグッズはこちら！
And here's the next item!
今回お披露目した3Dの姿がアクリルスタンドになります！
The 3D looks we debuted today are becoming acrylic stands!
先輩たちの3Dアクスタを持ってる人ならわかると思うんですが、かなり大きめのサイズとなっております。
If you own any of our seniors' 3D acrylic stands, you'll know they're quite a large size.
存在感ばっちりな私たちの3Dアクスタ、ぜひ手に取ってください。
Our 3D stands have a great presence, so please be sure to get yours.
こちらもホロフレと同じ今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、あわせてチェックしてくれると嬉しいです。
Just like the plushies, reservations start tonight at 22:00, so I'd love for you to check them out too.
続いては虎、おねがいします。
Next is Niko, please.
池袋にある... まずはこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ！
In Ikebukuro... first, please take a look at this! Here you go!
池袋にあるタワーレコード渋谷、サンシャインシティアルパ店ほか、全国のタワーレコード10店舗。
At Tower Records Shibuya, Sunshine City Alpa Branch in Ikebukuro, and 10 other locations nationwide.
そこで、FLOW GLOWのファーストアルバム発売を記念したポップアップの開催が決定！
We're holding a pop-up shop to celebrate the release of FLOW GLOW's first album!
今まで公式オンラインでしか手に入らなかったミックステープの1、2のほか、先ほど紹介したFGのホロフレ、グッズも盛りだくさんとなっております。
Besides Mixtapes 1 and 2, which were only online, we'll have plenty of goods, including the FG Holofre plushies!
また、期間中にグッズをお買い上げの方にはノベルティももらえる予定となっております。期間は1月20日から2月8日まで。
Also, customers will receive a novelty gift. The event runs from January 20th to February 8th.
グッズに関する詳しい情報やノベルティ条件などについては、12月中旬解説予定の特設ページをご覧ください。
For details on the goods and novelty requirements, please check the special page opening in mid-December.
最後はリオーナ、おねがいします。
Lastly, Riona, please.
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ！
Yes! Now, please take a look at this! Here you go!
この後、FLOW GLOW公式チャンネルのメンバーシップにて、アフタートークライブがあります。
After this, we'll have an After Talk Live exclusive to FLOW GLOW's official channel membership.
そっちにも足を運びたいなというそこのあなた、ぜひ今のうちにメンバーシップの登録をおねがいします。
For those of you who'd like to join us there, please consider joining our membership now!
そのアフタートークライブは、ここではなく別のステージからお届けします。
The After Talk Live will be broadcast from a different stage, not this one.
そこでしか聞けないライブの裏話とか、あとはファーストアルバムに収録されている曲の中からあの曲を披露したいと思います。
We'll share behind-the-scenes stories, and we'll also perform "that song" from our first album.
どう？ますます気になってきたんじゃない？
How about that? Are you getting more curious?
待ってるからね。また、私たち一人一人のチャンネルのメンバーシップでも、推しカメラ配信もあります。ぜひそっちも覗きに来てね。
We'll be waiting. Also, there'll be "Oshi Camera" streams on our individual memberships. Be sure to check those out!
そして、12月9日からの定期配信は3Dとなります！
And from December 9th, our regular streams will be in 3D!
さて皆さん、楽しい時間はあっという間ですね。
Well everyone, time flies when you're having fun.
そろそろライブも終了となります。
It's almost time to end the live.
ステージの思い出を写真に残したいんですけど。
I'd like to capture some memories of the stage in a photo.
お、任せて、すーちゃんど真ん中行くね。
Oh, leave it to me! Su-chan's going right in the middle.
よしよし、撮る撮る、いい写真撮るね。みんな並んでー。
Alright, let's take it. I'll take a great photo. Everyone, line up!
いくよー。はい、チーズ！パシャパシャパシャ...
Here we go. Say cheese! *Click click click*
よし、ありがとー。
Alright, thank you!
すーちゃんのおかげでね、素敵な思い出も撮れたところで。
Thanks to Su-chan, we've captured some wonderful memories.
ここでメンバー1人1人からファンの皆さんにメッセージを届けたいと思います。まずはすーちゃんから。
Now, each member would like to give a message to the fans. Starting with Su-chan.
はい、FLOW GLOW、そしてFLOW ME、ここまで一緒に走ってきてくれてありがとうございます。
Yes! FLOW GLOW and FLOW ME, thank you so much for running alongside us this far.
みんなのおかげで3Dになれたよー！
Thanks to everyone, we finally made it to 3D!
こっから先もいろんな思い出をみんなと一緒に作っていきたいです。よろしくね！
I want to keep making many more memories with all of you from here on. Thank you!
はい！
Hi!
いつも応援してくださるFuromi-minの皆さん、
To all the Furomi-min who always support us,
そしてメンバーみんな、いつもありがとう！
and to all the members, thank you always!
みんながいるからここまで来れました。
We've come this far because of all of you.
2周年目もみんな一緒にどんどん花道登っていきましょう！
Let's keep climbing the flowery path together in our second year!
これからもよろしくね！ほんまにありがとう！
We count on you from now on too! Thank you so much!
さ、続きまして、ニコはどうですか？
Now, next up, Niko, how about you?
FG！出会ってくれてありがとう！
FG! Thank you for meeting me!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そしてファンの皆さんも。
And to all the fans as well.
FLOWGLOWというダイヤモンドに気づいたあなた...天才じゃ！
You, who noticed the diamond that is FLOWGLOW... are a genius!
じゃあ！
Yeah!
これからもよろしくお、Furomi。ありがとう！
Keep supporting us, Furomi. Thank you!
ちはゆは？
How about Chihayu?
あ、はい、伊波乙揶でございます。
Ah, yes, this is Chihayu Isami.
いや本当にもね、今日という日をこの5人で迎えられたことが本当に嬉しく思いますし、
Honestly, I'm so happy that we five could welcome this day together,
このたくさんの方に我々の3Dお披露目を見守っていただけたことも本当に嬉しく思います。
and I'm truly grateful that so many people watched our 3D debut.
最後まで見ていただいてありがとうございます。
Thank you for watching until the very end.
ここからね、我々5人がもっともっと未来に向かって突き進んでいく姿、
From here on out, please don't miss us five
絶対に見逃さないでくださいね！
as we push forward into the future!
今日は本当にありがとう！メン限も待ってます！
Thank you so much for today! I'll see you in the member-only stream!
待ってます！待ってるよ！待ってるよ！
We'll be waiting! See ya! See ya!
はい最後、りっちゃん！
And finally, Ritchan!
はい。デビュー当初からずっと夢だった歌って踊る姿を、
Yes. It's been my dream since my debut to show myself singing and dancing,
届けられたことを本当に嬉しく思います。
and I'm so happy I could finally do that for you.
ここまで応援してくださって本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for supporting me until now.
そしてね、私たちはこれからも...ちょっとおいでよ？ちょっとおいでよみんな！
And, you know, we will continue to... wait, come here! Everyone, come here!
おいおいおい！
Hey, hey, hey!
まだ良いこと言うところだったのに！りおながふてくされちゃう！
I was about to say something good! Riona's gonna get sulky!
りっちゃん何か一言ある？
Ritchan, do you have any last words?
ちょっと男子ー？ちょっと男子ー！
Hey, you boys! Hey, boys!
ごめんね、いっぱい喋って？あのね、
Sorry, can I talk some more? Listen,
これからも私たち一人ひとりの歩みをみんなに見守ってほしいんだ！
I want everyone to keep watching over each of our individual journeys!
だからFLOWGLOWのことみんなこれからもよろしくね！
So please keep supporting FLOWGLOW from now on too!
よろしく！よろしくね！
We count on you! Count on us!
はいどうぞ、アンコール！
Alright, here we go, encore!
（騒ぎ声）
(Noise)
ここじゃないって！ちょっと早かったからね。
Not yet! That was a bit too early.
お別れする？これで終わりなの？
Are we saying goodbye? Is this the end?
バイバイしようか。最後に挨拶する？
Let's say bye-bye. Shall we do a final greeting?
（みんなで同意）
(Everyone agrees)
それでは私たち、せーの！
Alright then, on three!
FLOWGLOWでした！ありがとうございました！
We were FLOWGLOW! Thank you so much!
メン限も見だよ、んまっ！
Check out the member-only stream too, mwah!
うん！ビビ！大好きやで！ちゅ！
Yeah! Bibi! I love you! Chu!
本当にありがとう！んじょ！
Thank you so much! Njo!
ありがとう、んま！
Thank you, mwah!
ありがとう！おっ、誰？
Thank you! Oh, who's that?
FLOWGLOW! FLOWGLOW!
Furomi、アンコールありがとう！
Furomi, thank you for the encore!
今日は最高のライブでした！
Today was the best live performance!
みんな楽しんでくれたかな？
I hope everyone enjoyed it!
最後はこれ、やっぱりこの曲！
For the last one, it has to be this song!
FG ROADSTER!
縦型 V8 エンジン 第七感持ってる現時
Vertical V8 engine, currently with a seventh sense
Love するこの世界と前次 来この 5 人でゲームをチェンジ
Love this world and beyond, we five change the game
なる四輪発射せよ 皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Four wheels, launch! Thank you everyone, sarangheyo
操る二代のターンテーブル それ一番子号 FLOWGLOW
Operating two turntables, that's number one FLOWGLOW
ゼン！チャンスもセットだ　トウ！
Zen! A chance is set, ten!
ゼン！昇り上げる　チョウ！
Zen! Rising up to the peak!
ゼン！座布団踏んで　キショウ！
Zen! Stepping on the cushion, rise!
乗り込め FG ロードスター　特殊部隊集合　能力者
Board the FG Roadster, Special Forces assemble, power users
この歴史の名を彫る　彫刻家　ぶっちぎりで置き去り　観測車
Sculptors carving their names into this history, leaving observers in the dust
今高速でぶち抜いてく　大気圏
Now piercing through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの炎　揺れている　快気へ
Jet flames from the engine, flickering towards recovery
眼下に広がる大地　超えていく　回帰線
Crossing the Tropic, over the land spread out below
バックミラーに　ビッグブルーが映ってる　IPFY
Big Blue reflected in the rearview mirror, IPFY
ぶち上げたいから　飛んでく　うちら世代
Our generation taking off because we want to blast off
この燃料　朽ち果てない　ガス欠なし　寿司食べたい
This fuel won't run out, no running out of gas, I want to eat sushi
見据えてる　絶対　美徳　燃えてるメンバー　一同
Gazing at absolute virtue, all members burning bright
タライも　現在進行形　超えてく　世界規模
The tub is also in progress, crossing to a world scale
叶うはずだ　WASSA　心臓が　MONSTER
It must come true, WASSA! My heart is a MONSTER
エイリアン　時代になれ　FG PARTY HARD
Become an alien era, FG PARTY HARD
光る　TESLA ROADSTER　HEAVY BOOSTER
Glowing Tesla Roadster, Heavy Booster
目覚めていく　本能　青い炎
Awakening instinct, blue flame
BFF　レッツゴーアウト　トゲ抜きな　ゼロから
BFF, let's go out, pull out the thorns from zero
空まで　囚われ　走る　FG ロードスター
Captured all the way to the sky, racing FG Roadster
唸る　ブースター　ログロの　STAYS TO BE
Roaring booster, FLOW GLOW's stays to be
今　CHANGE TO ME
Now change to me
超弩級スーパーカー　ハンドルさばきは　玄人ハン
Super-dreadnought supercar, pro steering handling
爆走　重装　チューバッカ　次元が違う連中　バッカー
Roaring heavy-duty Chewbacca, a crowd from a different dimension
A-GO-NA　攻めてる　ギリギリ　モーター全開　ジリジリ
A-GO-NA attacking at the limit, motor at full throttle, on edge
ソーナー感知　ビキビキ　お肌ピチピチ
Sonar detection throbbing, skin looking fresh
タイヤ焦がして　ドーナツターン　弾け飛んでく　ドラム缶
Burning tires in a donut turn, drum cans flying off
顧客満足度高くて　ブチ上がってる　お客さん
High customer satisfaction, the audience is hyped
ゼロから最高到達点　足りてる　太陽光発電
Highest point from zero, enough solar power generation
探索する　この小惑星　超覚醒　突入　ボーナス点
Exploring this asteroid, super awakening, entering bonus points
一直線　伸びてる　ターボ　バイブレーション　MCのカード
Turbo vibration stretching in a straight line, MC's card
速度増し　上がってる　駆動　限界重力　凌駕し　上昇
Drivetrain speeding up, surpassing limit gravity, rising
開拓し　向かってく　フロンティア　旅立つ　ロードスター　オンリーワン
Opening up the frontier, Roadster departing, only one
アクセル踏み込んでく　ドンピシャ　飛んでく　一番星
Stepping on the accelerator perfectly, flying to the evening star
1億馬力の　中継点　火星のホテルが　休憩所
Relay point of 100 million horsepower, a hotel on Mars as a rest area
並んで走行　UFO　降り立つ　宇宙ステーション
Driving alongside UFOs, landing at the space station
物語は　継承　エイ！まるで　旧約聖書　エイ！
The story is passed on, hey! Like the Old Testament, hey!
この先何世紀も　成長　生き延びて　結果　ステイゴールド
Growing for centuries to come, surviving results, Stay Gold
叶うはずだ　WASSA　心臓が　MONSTER
It must come true, WASSA! My heart is a MONSTER
以上、私たち、FLOW GLOWでしたー！
That's all from us, FLOW GLOW!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
みんなのおかげで3Dだん！これからもよろしくね
Thanks to everyone, we're in 3D! Please continue to support us
これからも皆と楽しいこと、新しいスタート！！
Doing fun things with everyone from now on, a new start!!
FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE
MAKE IT, BREAK IT